profreetv.com 2018-11-03

# Privacy Policy - Watch Online TV - Live TV - Free Online TV

By using our site, you consent to our Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of these changes. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of these changes. If you want to communicate with us about our policy, please contact us thru our contact section.

We use cookies to improve the use of our website.

This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computers hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. Google Analytics provides an opt out tool to provide website visitors more choice on how their data is collected. If you want to opt-out, download and install the add-on for your current web browser. The Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on is available for Microsoft Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari and Opera. Get the Google Analytics Opt out Browser Add-on [click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). For further information you can read Google's privacy policy [here](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. By using this Site, you agree that advertising companies place these types of cookies on your device.

You should make sure you are aware of how third parties will use cookies by checking the third party's cookie policy. Below you can find list of partners that might be dropping cookies.  

If you want more information or if you wish to turn off/on the use of cookies set by individual advertising companies please visit one of the following websites:  
[www.youronlinechoises.com](https://www.youronlinechoices.com/)[  
www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

Disabling/enabling, deleting cookies via your browser  
Click on any of the browser links below for instructions.  
[Mozilla Firefox  
](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies) [Google Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&p=cpn_cookies)  

You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer.
